[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "The man who brought you this?", "question_tokens": ["The", "man", "who", "brought", "you", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "\"TV Guide\" gave out an award several years ago to the 50 worst shows in the history of television.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "TV", "Guide", "''", "gave", "out", "an", "award", "several", "years", "ago", "to", "the", "50", "worst", "shows", "in", "the", "history", "of", "television", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "She came home from the hospital this morning and she is doing just terrific and I want to thank you and everybody out there for all their prayers.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "came", "home", "from", "the", "hospital", "this", "morning", "and", "she", "is", "doing", "just", "terrific", "and", "I", "want", "to", "thank", "you", "and", "everybody", "out", "there", "for", "all", "their", "prayers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "So if you were the president in the time span we're looking at, the next three or four months, and you have the intelligence that suggested that Iran was at the point of enriching uranium that they needed to get to a nuclear capacity here, and you heard the Israeli would definitely going to go in with strikes, would you sanction American military strikes as well at the same time?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "you", "were", "the", "president", "in", "the", "time", "span", "we", "'re", "looking", "at", ",", "the", "next", "three", "or", "four", "months", ",", "and", "you", "have", "the", "intelligence", "that", "suggested", "that", "Iran", "was", "at", "the", "point", "of", "enriching", "uranium", "that", "they", "needed", "to", "get", "to", "a", "nuclear", "capacity", "here", ",", "and", "you", "heard", "the", "Israeli", "would", "definitely", "going", "to", "go", "in", "with", "strikes", ",", "would", "you", "sanction", "American", "military", "strikes", "as", "well", "at", "the", "same", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "The first thing I'd be doing is giving a speech similar to Reagan's evil empire speech.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "thing", "I", "'d", "be", "doing", "is", "giving", "a", "speech", "similar", "to", "Reagan", "'s", "evil", "empire", "speech", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Prayer Breakfast"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Are you -- are you feeling a bit threatened there that the president has become all religious suddenly?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "feeling", "a", "bit", "threatened", "there", "that", "the", "president", "has", "become", "all", "religious", "suddenly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, you know, look, it was at a National Prayer Breakfast, that's if you're going to -- a president is going to become all religious, that's a good place to become all religious.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "look", ",", "it", "was", "at", "a", "National", "Prayer", "Breakfast", ",", "that", "'s", "if", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "--", "a", "president", "is", "going", "to", "become", "all", "religious", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "place", "to", "become", "all", "religious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Are you -- are you cynical when you hear that, the people say, I pray all the time and I'm on my knees every morning, but I don't actually go to church?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "cynical", "when", "you", "hear", "that", ",", "the", "people", "say", ",", "I", "pray", "all", "the", "time", "and", "I", "'m", "on", "my", "knees", "every", "morning", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "actually", "go", "to", "church", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "You know, everybody practices their faith in a way that is comfortable for them.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "everybody", "practices", "their", "faith", "in", "a", "way", "that", "is", "comfortable", "for", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "How did you feel when you saw the Trumpster giving his endorsement?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "saw", "the", "Trumpster", "giving", "his", "endorsement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I'm glad he gave it to him, not me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "glad", "he", "gave", "it", "to", "him", ",", "not", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What are your expectations in Nevada?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "expectations", "in", "Nevada", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Nevada"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "And finally one word answer please, Giants or Patriots?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", "one", "word", "answer", "please", ",", "Giants", "or", "Patriots", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Neither.", "answer_tokens": ["Neither", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Jerry won't read them because he's not on Twitter, right?", "question_tokens": ["Jerry", "wo", "n't", "read", "them", "because", "he", "'s", "not", "on", "Twitter", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "The separate part becomes a little blurred, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "separate", "part", "becomes", "a", "little", "blurred", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 208, "question": "He doesn't really care, does he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "really", "care", ",", "does", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "It's not --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What is the Obama mantra for America, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "Obama", "mantra", "for", "America", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I don't think it's a bumper sticker so I don't think it's one slogan.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "bumper", "sticker", "so", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "one", "slogan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Well, you get too touch about it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "get", "too", "touch", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "No, that's -- I should just tell you that was exactly 30 years ago yesterday.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "--", "I", "should", "just", "tell", "you", "that", "was", "exactly", "30", "years", "ago", "yesterday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'82, February 1st"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Was it really?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "That I announced for governor, yes, back in '82, February 1st.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "I", "announced", "for", "governor", ",", "yes", ",", "back", "in", "'82", ",", "February", "1st", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "In all your -- in all your experience, is this any nastier, the Republican race, than every other Republican-Democrat nominee race for presidential election?", "question_tokens": ["In", "all", "your", "--", "in", "all", "your", "experience", ",", "is", "this", "any", "nastier", ",", "the", "Republican", "race", ",", "than", "every", "other", "Republican-Democrat", "nominee", "race", "for", "presidential", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Not particularly nastier, we have now obviously the 24/7 coverage and so much more money spent on advertising that the commercials are so much rougher.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "particularly", "nastier", ",", "we", "have", "now", "obviously", "the", "24/7", "coverage", "and", "so", "much", "more", "money", "spent", "on", "advertising", "that", "the", "commercials", "are", "so", "much", "rougher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", ":"], "qSentId": 313, "question": "And that's to the detriment of the country, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "to", "the", "detriment", "of", "the", "country", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Yes - -", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "-", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Washington"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "I mean, all this -- I mean, why would any young person have respect for our institutions when all our leaders do is disparage anyone that decides to get involved?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "all", "this", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "why", "would", "any", "young", "person", "have", "respect", "for", "our", "institutions", "when", "all", "our", "leaders", "do", "is", "disparage", "anyone", "that", "decides", "to", "get", "involved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Also, I mean, if you look at the way that America has tried to go around the world showing off the virtues of a fair and free democratic political system, it doesn't say a lot for that fair and free democratic system if people look at Washington and see this paralysis because they all hate each other so much.", "answer_tokens": ["Also", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "the", "way", "that", "America", "has", "tried", "to", "go", "around", "the", "world", "showing", "off", "the", "virtues", "of", "a", "fair", "and", "free", "democratic", "political", "system", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "say", "a", "lot", "for", "that", "fair", "and", "free", "democratic", "system", "if", "people", "look", "at", "Washington", "and", "see", "this", "paralysis", "because", "they", "all", "hate", "each", "other", "so", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "When you watch these scenes -- be honest, Jerry -- do you ever wish you had stayed in politics?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watch", "these", "scenes", "--", "be", "honest", ",", "Jerry", "--", "do", "you", "ever", "wish", "you", "had", "stayed", "in", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ":", "VB", "JJS", ",", "NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, I mean, every day I -- I mean I love these political things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "every", "day", "I", "--", "I", "mean", "I", "love", "these", "political", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "But shouldn't be an absolutely number one priority for whoever wins the election in November, education, education, education?", "question_tokens": ["But", "should", "n't", "be", "an", "absolutely", "number", "one", "priority", "for", "whoever", "wins", "the", "election", "in", "November", ",", "education", ",", "education", ",", "education", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.S. Congress"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "It really is time -- never mind the world, which is what the book is obviously aimed at, that American leaders collaborated, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "really", "is", "time", "--", "never", "mind", "the", "world", ",", "which", "is", "what", "the", "book", "is", "obviously", "aimed", "at", ",", "that", "American", "leaders", "collaborated", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Actually, if you want an example of failure to collaborate, all you want to do is look at the U.S. Congress, in terms of the fiasco that that body has become.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "if", "you", "want", "an", "example", "of", "failure", "to", "collaborate", ",", "all", "you", "want", "to", "do", "is", "look", "at", "the", "U.S.", "Congress", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "fiasco", "that", "that", "body", "has", "become", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Panetta"]}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "And from a police point of view, how concerned would you be if you were running one of these major cities right now, about some kind of pre- emptive attack from Iran or a retaliatory attack on the people of Los Angeles, Boston or New York?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "a", "police", "point", "of", "view", ",", "how", "concerned", "would", "you", "be", "if", "you", "were", "running", "one", "of", "these", "major", "cities", "right", "now", ",", "about", "some", "kind", "of", "pre-", "emptive", "attack", "from", "Iran", "or", "a", "retaliatory", "attack", "on", "the", "people", "of", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "Boston", "or", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Well, I think the most significant comments are coming from the Israelis, the head of Israeli intelligence, who is clearly indicating they believe that it's not a two-year period of time we're talking about, as Mr. Panetta has indicted, but realistically one year.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "most", "significant", "comments", "are", "coming", "from", "the", "Israelis", ",", "the", "head", "of", "Israeli", "intelligence", ",", "who", "is", "clearly", "indicating", "they", "believe", "that", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "two-year", "period", "of", "time", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", ",", "as", "Mr.", "Panetta", "has", "indicted", ",", "but", "realistically", "one", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Los Angeles", "Boston", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120202pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "How far do you go in allowing them to express that freedom and right to protest, particularly where they have public support, and where they cross the line and you have to come down firmly?", "question_tokens": ["How", "far", "do", "you", "go", "in", "allowing", "them", "to", "express", "that", "freedom", "and", "right", "to", "protest", ",", "particularly", "where", "they", "have", "public", "support", ",", "and", "where", "they", "cross", "the", "line", "and", "you", "have", "to", "come", "down", "firmly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, looking at the recent Occupy Wall Street movement, the movement of police against those activities, the encampments or the demonstrations or the marches, we firs rely on political decisions to be made by mayors, by governors, who, in effect, authorize us to take action.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "looking", "at", "the", "recent", "Occupy", "Wall", "Street", "movement", ",", "the", "movement", "of", "police", "against", "those", "activities", ",", "the", "encampments", "or", "the", "demonstrations", "or", "the", "marches", ",", "we", "firs", "rely", "on", "political", "decisions", "to", "be", "made", "by", "mayors", ",", "by", "governors", ",", "who", ",", "in", "effect", ",", "authorize", "us", "to", "take", "action", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]